THEOPHILUS TENA GOPREGHA

+2348057974094, +2348168242862 | tenagopregha@gmail.com Lagos, Nigeria LinkedIn | Dribbble | Twitter

PROFILE SUMMARY

Innovative Product and User-Experience Designer with the proven know-how to combine creative and usability viewpoints resulting in world-class Web and Mobile applications. Experienced at driving a user experience from start to finish that delivers results and connects emotionally. Blends technology skills with extensive interaction models, user interface specifications, and analytical abilities to evolve product strategy. Highly familiar with the workings of Figma, Adobe XD, Framer Motion, Html5, CSS, JavaScript, ReactJs, Node, and Github.

CORE COMPETENCIES

- Usability Engineering
- Interaction Design
- Frontend Development
- User-flow

- User Experience
- Figma
- Prototyping
- Responsive design

- Wireframing
- UX & UI Design
- Empathy

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Wigi Software (Product Designer - Full-Time) - Nigeria

Nov. 2021 - Present

- Develops the high-level product road map, listing out the functionalities to be completed within the broader time frames.
- Managed 3+ employees and engaged with 20+ clients across industries.
- Pitched web and mobile prototypes to 5+ organisations with 90% success rate
- Analysed project requirements and data and implemented website strategy.

9jaMall (Frontend Developer - Contract) - Nigeria

Nov. 2021 - Feb. 2022

- Converted the user interface design of 9jaMall to code using html, css and javascript.
- Responsitivity: Coverted the desktop code to be responsive across all device screens.

Yefepere (Frontend Developer - Intern) - Nigeria

April. 2021 - Aug. 2021

- Designed custom emails for <u>Yefepere</u> using ejs.
- Responsitivity: Made the design responsive across all screens.

Wigi Software (Product Design Intern) - Nigeria

April. 2021 - Oct. 2021

- Develops the high-level product road map, listing out the functionalities to be completed within the broader time frames.
- Managed 3+ employees and engaged with 20+ clients across industries.
- Pitched web and mobile prototypes to 5+ organisations with 90% success rate
- Analysed project requirements and data and implemented website strategy.

PROJECTS

•	Wigi Softwares	Frontend Developer	2022
•	UslProject	Frontend Developer	2022
•	TedxSwaliMarketRoad	Frontend Developer	2022

EDUCATION

• Frontend Web Developer - Wigi Academy

Computer Science – Federal University Otuoke

2021

Present